there's a tornado hurry up and get
inside don't hit your ass on the way out
[ __ ] give me those slipper
what on earth was that those those
slippers were a birthday present from
Daddy tomorrow is my birthday
you munchkin villagers are going to
regret ever making an enemy of me I'll
be back for my slipper
here's Sonia you better watch your ass
can you guys give me my oil can Haney
Knuckles look Meriden
you
yet you like that don't you boy
I bet you like having oil rubbed on your
butt cheeks how long is this going to
take perhaps I should give you a
spanking for disobeying me
oh my goodness you just ruin all over me
now my body is all slippery hey what's
this
he whoops that picture must have fallen
out of my bag it's beautiful did you
draw this yourself